

Mobile: +56 9 56466435

E-mail: constanza.lledo@gmail.com

WHO AM I?

As an interior and graphic designer, I am passionate about creating spaces and products which enhance the quality of people's lives. Being a designer allows me to have an expert and critical view on how to make communities feel happier and more comfortable with their surroundings. The needs of communities and people are the engine of my work. Therefore, to me it is extremely important to work alongside other professionals in order to achieve better results, especially when it comes to something so importante as how people interact with their environment. I strongly believe good design must be available for everyone.

I am a perseverant, trustworthy and a fully committed person, who works towards achieving my goals. Being empathic, respectful and proactive are some of the qualities that make me a great team member.

O

SOFTWARE SKILLS



















SHORT COURSES

2017 Pottery - Wheel throwing & Hand built Waikato Society of Potters, Hamilton, New Zealand.

2014 Advanced English course Waikato Institute of Education, Hamilton, New Zealand.

2011 Xilography - Santiago, Chile.

2010 Textile screen-printing - Santiago, Chile.

2009 Loom weaving - Santiago, Chile.

2008 Bookbinding - Santiago, Chile.

2005 Photography - Santiago, Chile.

LINKS

WINTEC - 2016 Interior Design final portfolio: https://issuu.com/cdlv.studio/docs/wintec_constanza_portfolio

Graphic Design final project: http://jureltipocarbon.cl/

To download my Graphic Design thesis: http://repositorio.uchile.cl/handle/2250/116549

REFERENCE

Dominic Buckell -Director at Chibnall Buckell Team Architects dominic.buckell@cbmarchitects.co.nz +64 2 74 747 265

EXPERIENCE -



Internships in the interior design industry -Hamilton, New Zealand

2012 - 2014Freelance Graphic Designer -Santiago, Chile

2012 April - August Graphic Designer for Agencia Felicidad (Internship) -Santiago, Chile.

EDUCATION

2015 - 2016

Interior Design - Best Overall Student Waikato Institute of Technology (WINTEC) -Hamilton, New Zealand

2007 - 2013

Graphic Design - Graduated with distintion University of Chile - Santiago, Chile.

ACHIEVEMENTS

2017 Best Overall Student - Interior Design Received at WINTEC - Hamilton, New Zealand

2016 Interior Design Eco Award (by Design Engine Architects) Received at WINTEC - Hamilton, New Zealand

O

2016 Academic Excellence Fee Scholarship Received at WINTEC - Hamilton, New Zealand

LANGUAGES

Spanish - Native English - Advanced (Overall 7.5, IELTS 2018)



Teléfono: +56 9 56466435 **E-mail:** constanza.lledo@gmail.com

¿QUIÉN SOY?

Como diseñadora gráfica y de interiores, me apasiona crear espacios y productos que mejoran la calidad de vida de las personas. Ser diseñadora significa tener una visión experta y crítica en cómo hacer que grupos de personas se sientan más felices y cómodas en sus ambientes. Las necesidades de personas o comunidades son el motor de mi trabajo. Por esto, para mí es sumamente importante trabajar en conjunto con otros profesionales, lo que permite lograr mejores resultados; especialmente al tratarse de algo tan importante como cómo las personas interactúan con su entorno. Creo firmemente que el buen diseño debe estar disponible para todos.

Soy una persona perseverante, confiable y comprometida, que trabajo para alcanzar mis metas. Algunas cualidades que me convierten en una buena integrante de equipo son la empatía, el respeto y la proactividad.

MANEJO DE SOFTWARES



















CURSOS

2017 Cerámica - en torno y modelado a mano Waikato Society of Potters, Hamilton, Nueva Zelanda

2014 Curso avanzado de inglés Waikato Institute of Education, Hamilton, Nueva Zelanda

2011 Xilografía - Santiago, Chile.

2010 Serigrafía - Santiago, Chile.

2009 Tejido a telar - Santiago, Chile.

2008 Encuadernación - Santiago, Chile.

2005 Fotografía - Santiago, Chile.

LINKS

WINTEC - 2016 Diseño de Interiores Portafolio final: https://issuu.com/cdlv.studio/docs/wintec_constanza_portfolio

Proyecto de título de Diseño Gráfico: http://jureltipocarbon.cl/

Para descargar mi tésis de Diseño Gráfico: http://repositorio.uchile.cl/handle/2250/116549

REFERENCIA

Dominic Buckell -Director en Chibnall Buckell Team Architects dominic.buckell@cbmarchitects.co.nz +64 2 74 747 265

EXPERIENCIA -



2017 Febrero - 2019 Junio

Diseñadora de Interiores en Chibnall Buckell Team Architects -Hamilton, Nueva Zelanda

2016

Prácticas profesionales en la industria del diseño de interiores -Hamilton, Nueva Zelanda

2012 - 2014

Diseñadora Gráfica freelance Santiago, Chile

2012 Abril - Agosto

Práctica profesional de Diseño Gráfico en Agencia Felicidad - Santiago, Chile.

FORMACIÓN

2015 - 2016

Diseño de Interiores - Mejor egresada de la promoción Waikato Institute of Technology (WINTEC) - Hamilton, Nueva Zelanda

2007 - 2013

Diseño Gráfico - Titulada con Distinción Universidad de Chile - Santiago, Chile.

LOGROS

2017 Mejor egresada de la promoción - Diseño de Interiores Recibido en WINTEC - Hamilton, Nueva Zelanda

2016 Interior Design Eco Award (entregado por Design Engine Architects) Recibido en WINTEC - Hamilton, Nueva Zelanda

2016 Beca por excelencia académica Recibido en WINTEC - Hamilton, Nueva Zelanda

IDIOMAS -

Español - Nativo

Inglés - Avanzado (Promedio 7.5, IELTS 2018)